"伤心女士书友会"又在看
The Sad Lady Book Club is reading
"五十度灰"了
Fifty Shades of Grey again.
全场的座位都湿了
There's not a dry seat in the house.
如果那些女士这么喜欢轻度折磨
If those ladies are that into light torture,
她们就应该申请我们的工作
they should just apply for our jobs.
嘿
Hey.
哦 你们俩真让人羡慕
Aww, you two are so adorable.
就像罗密欧和朱丽叶 只是没有美好的未来
Like Romeo and Juliet, but without the bright future.
对...
Yeah...
我要他离开餐厅
I want him out of the diner.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
在这间餐厅工作的所有人
Anyone who works in this diner
都像是坐在斯玛特车里的胖子
is like a fat guy in a Smart car.
永远别想出去
You can never get out.
没错
It's true.
1962年 我为了一杯咖啡来到这里
I came in here in 1962 for a cup of coffee.
有人让我兑开一美元 我就没离开过了
Someone asked me to break a dollar, and I never left.
听我说 和同一个人一起生活 工作 睡觉
Look. Living, working, and sleeping with the same guy
绝不是个好主意
is never a good idea.
不信去问希拉里·克林顿
Just talk to Hillary Clinton.
我想我还是能炒掉一个洗碗工的
I guess I can get a dishwasher fired.
当我还是有钱人时 我曾把沃尔夫刚·帕克从他自己的餐厅炒掉
When I was rich, I got Wolfgang Puck fired from Wolfgang Puck.
沃尔夫刚·帕克: 美国加州第一名厨 开办了同名餐厅
去做吧 Max!
Get yours, Max!
先干 再走
Hit it then quit it.
在我二三十岁的时候 这方法对我很管用
That strategy served me well in my 20s and 30s.
晚上好 女士们
Evening, ladies.
七十岁时也是
Also, my 70s.
破产姐妹花 第四季第19集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hdscg.com/ ==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 。沫   校对: Shadow
翻译: morning  Olio  CC
上菜
Pick up.
不上也行
Or don't.
谁在乎呢?
Who gives a crap?
有人心情不好哦 怎么了 Oleg?
Well, someone's in a bad mood. What's wrong, Oleg?
Axe身体喷雾停产了吗?
Did they discontinue making Axe body spray?
不许开这个玩笑
Don't even kid.
不是 我心情不好是因为我现在没有做爱
No. I'm cranky because I'm not having sex right now.
是啊 我还想着 在你说话时能看见你的两只手
Yeah. I thought it was weird seeing both your hands
真是奇怪
while you were talking.
Sophie的主意 这是某种古老的波兰礼仪
Sophie's idea. It's some old Polish ritual.
新郎和新娘在婚礼前的30天里
The bride and groom remain chaste for 30 days
不能做爱
before the wedding.
显然 在婚礼上伤心的
Apparently, the "something blue" at the wedding
应该是我的蛋蛋
has got to be my balls.
这么说 你是在练习禁欲
So, you're practicing celibacy.
我在努力 但是女人无处不在
I'm trying, but there are women everywhere.
我觉得自己像是阴道群里的公牛
I feel like a bull in a vagina shop.
安静 听我说!
Hear ye, hear ye!
我要公布餐厅的一个重要改进!
I'm unveiling a major improvement to the diner!
我们会想你的 Han
Well, we'll miss you, Han.
想得美 Max 但是就像瑞安·西克莱斯特
Nice try, Max, but like Ryan Seacrest,
"美国偶像"主持人
我会一直在这里
I'll be here forever.
现在 请所有人做一件你们还没在推特上完成的事情
Now, will you all please do what you have yet to do on Twitter
跟我来(关注我)
and follow me?
你也是 Earl
You too, Earl.
天啊 但愿这是好事
Hell, this better be good.
我做的每件事都可能是最后一件
Every step I take could be my last.
现在...
And now...
不用说无脑台词...
Without further a-douche...
准备好让你的心怒放了吗?
Ready to have your minds blown?
这里插一句 我准备好让一切怒放了
At this point, I'm ready to have anything blown.
当当!
Ta-da!
这是我收到过的最糟糕的礼物
That is the worst gift I ever received
去年 我儿子买给我的是棺材
and last year, my son bought me a coffin.
这个真的很棒 因为不是给你的
This works out great then, because it's not for you.
是给Nash的
It's for Nash.
哦 那真的是很好
Oh, well, that's real nice.
因为Max家的淋浴器完全坏了
Because the shower at Max's place doesn't work at all.
你最好认为它很好
You better believe it's nice.
这可是"喷头5000"
That's the Spritzy 5000.
"洗碗工周报"给它评了四个盘子的高分
Dishwasher Weekly gave it four out of four Dishies.
你知道我们的烤箱坏了 对吧?
You know our oven doesn't work, right?
嘿 老板娘 要是我们努力工作 我们也有礼物吗?
Hey, boss lady, if we work hard, do we get a gift?
要是你努力工作 那我就死时无子女
If you work hard, I'll die childless
而且我会惊讶地张着嘴死掉
with my mouth frozen open in shock.
对 我说过了!
Yeah, I went there!
Nash工作努力 所以只有他能使用我漂亮的管子!
Nash works hard, so only he may handle my beautiful hose!
要是他用上了Han的管子
Well, if he's handling Han's hose,
那他不可能被炒了
he's never getting fired.
好了 站上来 Nash
Okay. Step up here, Nash.
我给你展示下 这小东西能做什么
I'll show you what this puppy can do.
目前 这小东西拿不到水管
So far the puppy can't reach the hose.
帮个忙
A little help.
哦 没什么比一个帅哥抱着个婴儿更可爱的了
Aww, there's nothing cuter than a hot guy holding a baby.
现在只要抓着它 挤到它喷出来就可以了
Now just grab that thing and squeeze it till it sprays.
在婚礼前 请暂停使用"抓""挤"
Move to call a moratorium on the words "grab," "squeeze,"
"喷"这些词
and "sprays" till the wedding.
天啊! 真性感
Damn! That's hot.
我什么都不做 就能看到他裤子里的东西
And me without any singles to stuff down his pants.
我还是去男厕所弄干吧
Well, I better go dry off in the men's room.
别占着茅坑太久
Don't be too long in that stall.
我下次中间休息时 还要跟拿着蓝多湖黄油袋子的女士
I've got a date with the Land O'Lakes butter package lady
约会
on my next break.
对不起 女士们 我全湿了
Oh. Pardon me, ladies. I'm all wet.
Max? 你看到我眼前的景象了吗?
Max? Are you seeing what I'm seeing?
那些女生看着他 就好像他是Sizzler's(泰国)餐厅的
Those ladies looking at him like he's a senior special
高级服务生?
at Sizzler's?
我们也许不能让Nash被炒
We might not be able to get Nash fired,
但我们可以让他被雇为时尚模特
but we can get him hired as a fashion model.
看看她们的脸
Look at their faces.
他可以成为CK(时装品牌)的未来巨星
He could be the future bulge of Calvin Klein.
你现在在聊未来吗?
Now you're talking about the future?
你怎么就不肯承认 我们因一个很垃圾的礼物
Why can't you just accept that we are stuck
而陷入困境了呢?
with a really crappy present?
不准说"喷头5000"的坏话!
Quit trash-talking the Spritzy 5000!
下午好 欢迎光临"糕潮"
Good afternoon. Welcome to The High.
我去让人给你拿杯水
I'll have somebody get you some water.
不是我 因为我不做这种事了
Not me, 'cause I'm past that.
也就在这里不做
You know, here.
我觉得我又为了我们老板 让一个拉拉相亲会的人
I think I just sat another one of those lesbian blind-dates
坐下了
for our boss.
在外面给皮条客干活真不容易
It's hard out there for a pimp.
你为什么以为我不干拉皮条了?
Why do you think I got out of pimping?
因为有人在我头上爆了一个啤酒瓶
That and someone broke a beer bottle over my head.
你给Nash找到模特工作了吗?
So, did you get Nash a modeling job yet?
我正在找
I'm working on it.
这不是给泰拉·班克斯(超模)打个电话就行的
It's not like I can just call Tyra Banks.
那是我打过去的时候 她的人说的
Well, that's what her people said when I called.
呃 电话治疗进行了好久
Ugh, phone therapy ran long.
显然 罗茜(主持)离开"观点"节目给我带来的问题
Apparently I have more issues than I realized
比想象中更多
about Rosie leaving The View.
我的约会对象们到了吗?
Are my dates here yet?
不要告诉我 是她 她 或者她
Please don't tell me it's her, her, or her.
就是她 她 以及她
It's her, her, and her.
赶走她们
Lose them.
我要怎么赶走她们?
How am I supposed to get rid of them?
大家想让拉拉走的时候怎么说的 就怎么说
Just say what anyone says when they want a lesbian to leave,
"外面有辆斯巴鲁 可以拿到票哦"
"There's a Subaru outside that's about to get a ticket."
你要是在十年前告诉我
If you had you told me, ten years ago,
我会上一个约会网站 叫"拉拉约会"
I'd be on a dating site called "Lez Meet Up,"
我就会告诉那位跟我结过婚的年轻牧师
I would've told the youth pastor I was married to,
"你已经疯了"
"You've lost your mind."
哦 我刚收到
Oh, I just got some interest
Del Monico模特经纪公司的回复
from the Del Monico Modeling Agency.
但他要有照片去面试
But for the interview, he needs photos.
不能是你手机里他屁股的照片
And not just the pictures of his butt on your phone.
好吧 你搞定
Fine, you handle it.
我对于模特行业的了解仅限于
The only thing I know about modeling is
几年前 我曾是医疗网上带状疱疹的封面模特
a couple of years ago, I was the face of shingles on WebMD.
姑娘们 来让我拍照的时机刚刚好
Girls, perfect timing to ask me to do this photo shoot.
联邦调查局上周刚把我的相机还给我
The FBI just gave me my camera back last week.
他们把你的相机还给你了
Oh, so you get your camera back,
可我却还在等那一公斤的
but I'm still waiting on that kilo of coke
我花了几小时小心塞满我屁股的可卡因?
that I spent hours carefully filling my butt with?
我来改一下设置
Let me just change the settings.
这台相机原本是用来拍摄800英尺(250米)外的照片的
This camera is used to taking pictures from 800 feet away.
把照片还给我们 Oleg!
And we want those pictures back, Oleg!
嘿 大家好!
Hey, everybody!
就管我这叫"高潮期"吧
Just call me "rush hour traffic"
因为我太饥渴了
'cause I sure am horny.
哦 Caroline 真不知道你这么多多
Oh, Caroline, I do not know how you go years, and years,
多多多多年
and years, and years, and years, and years
是怎么守住贞操的
without doing the nasty.
这才这么多多年
It's only been years and years.
- 拜托  - 多多多年
- Come on.  - And years.
我想来份鲜肉三明治
Well, I could go for a brisket sandwich.
打烊了 Sophie
We're closed, Sophie.
我知道 我自己有带
I know. I got one in my purse.
还有你们为什么在这肮脏的洗碗间里拍大片?
And why are you doing the photo shoot in this skanky dishroom?
因为我们打算用"性感洗碗工"的主题
Because we're going with the "hot dishwasher" angle.
经纪公司说每个模特都要有勾引人的噱头
The agency said every model needs a hook.
比如辛迪·克劳馥的美人痣
Yeah, like how Cindy Crawford has a beauty mark
还有安娜·妮可·史密斯的死
and Anna Nicole Smith is dead.
没错 我妹妹在波兰也是名模特 她也有"勾"引人的地方
Yeah, yeah. My sister is a model in Poland and she has a hook.
就是她的左手 用来烤肉串一级棒
It's her left hand, yeah. It's is also great for kabobs.
出来吧 Nash!
Come on, Nash!
脚步里带点爱尔兰的活力
Put a little Irish Spring in your step.
我有点小紧张
I'm a little nervous.
我唯一一次拍照是在学校
The only other time I had my picture taken was at school.
神父说他需要一个光膀子的人来点名
The priest said he needed a shirtless one for the roll call.
你上的是什么学校 "猎捕恋童癖"圣母学院?
Where did he go to school, Our Lady of To Catch a Predator?
美国真人秀节目
喔 真的好性感
Wow. You sure look hot.
说话注意点 Sophie
Careful, Sophie.
这是我的小鲜肉
That's my brisket.
我说的可不是这位丹尼尔·戴-卢瑟
I'm not talking about Daniel Day-Loser here.
丹尼尔·戴-刘易斯 奥斯卡影帝 爱尔兰籍
我说的是Oleg
I'm talking about Oleg.
你全身流汗就像是条被太阳
You are sweating like an old knockwurst
烤出油的老香肠
that has been left out in the sun.
让人垂涎欲滴
It's really breathtaking.
好了 Nash 拿着水管站在这
Okay, Nash, stand over here near the hose
摆出目光呆滞的性感面孔
and give me hot face, dead eyes.
就像我把白加黑的日夜片混着吃一样
You know, like me when I mix NyQuil and DayQuil.
我管它叫下午片
I call it AfternoonQuil.
好了 我要开始拍摄了
Okay. Now I'm gonna start shooting.
对 摄起来 宝贝! 摄起来!
Yeah. Shoot, baby! Shoot!
你觉得怎样?
What do you think?
表情的确僵硬 但不是无神那种
Well, he's stiff, but not in the good way.
啊 真是受不了
Ugh, this is painful.
他就像是没星范的苏珊·鲍尔
He's like Susan Boyle without the star quality.
苏珊·鲍尔: 因参加"英国达人秀"而一夜爆红
我们得弄成像上次那样
We need a little of what he had the other day.
你之后会为此感谢我的
You'll thank me for this later.
对 Nash 就是这样!
Yes, Nash, yes!
把衣服撕破!
Tear your shirt!
- 就是这样  - 哦 就是这样
- Yeah, yeah.  - Oh, yeah, yeah.
住手!
Stop!
这里什么情况?
What the hell is happening in here?
我没同意把餐厅借给你们
I didn't give anyone permission to use my diner
拍大片啊
for a photo shoot.
别激动
Calm down.
我们想帮他找份模特的工作
We are trying to get him a modeling job.
他有工作! 他是我的头号员工
He has a job! He's my number one worker.
就像医生在你妈生你时说的话
Like the doctor said to your mother when you were born,
运气不佳
tough break.
你们两个坏家伙什么都不肯给我!
You two crows don't let me have anything!
好了 Nash 模特面试的一部分
Okay, Nash, part of the model audish
是看你在广告里的表现
is to see how you'd be as a performer in commercials,
还有电影 还有别的没人看的东西
and movies, and other things people don't watch anymore.
显然 作为新手
Now, obviously, right out of the gate,
你比不上Aflac广告里的白鸭子
you're not gonna be as good as that duck who says "Aflac,"
但你至少要比本·阿弗莱克强
but you've got to be at least as good as Ben Affleck.
我能帮上忙 有段时间 我的演艺事业挺辉煌的
I can help. For a time, I had a rich acting career.
最开始是"安妮"里的一个小角色
It started with a starring role in Annie,
最后扮演的是罗莎·帕克斯
and ended when I portrayed Rosa Parks
罗莎·帕克斯: 黑人人权运动之母
因为这个考虑不周的高中舞台剧
in an ill-advised high school production
引起了有色人种协进会的调查
that led to an investigation by the NAACP.
哦 这是早餐麦片的广告!
Ooh, this is a commercial for breakfast cereal!
啊! 每个演员的梦想啊!
Ah! Every actor's dream!
嘿 Nash 读一下
Hey, Nash, read this.
想象自己是詹姆斯·迪恩
Think James Dean.
詹姆斯·迪恩: 好莱坞青春偶像
但要有生气 还要假装在吃可可米花
But alive and eating Cocoa Puffs.
"美味的可可米花是任何
"Cocoa Puffs are a delicious part
营养搭配的早餐的必备品"
of any well-balanced breakfast."
我在想要怎么说得客气...
I'm trying to find a nice way to say...
你逊毙了 伙计
You suck, bro.
你... 你懂吧
You... you get it.
在通常不吃巧克力的时段
You know the thrill of eating chocolate
吃巧克力的兴奋感
at a traditionally non-chocolatey time of day.
往这方向想
Let's tap into that.
好的 从头开始
Okay. Take it from the top.
但这一次 疯狂(杜鹃)点
And this time, go cuckoo.
麦片的吉祥物
我为可可米花狂
Go cuckoo for Cocoa Puffs.
"美味的可可米花..."
"Cocoa Puffs are a delicious..."
打住
Stop.
别这样子来 这不是葡萄干麦片
Don't phone this in. It's not Raisin Bran.
"美味的割口迷花..."
"Pocoa Cuffs are a delicious..."
"割口迷花"?
"Pocoa Cuffs"?
割口迷花?
Pocoa Cuffs?
我受不了这些糟糕透顶的业余者 Caroline
I just can't with these rank amateurs, Caroline.
Max 冷静点
Max, calm down.
这是麦片广告的试演
It's a fake tryout for a cereal commercial,
不是"舞蹈妈妈"
not Dance Moms.
舞蹈真人秀 其中的舞蹈老师略毒舌
我太紧张了 我不是演戏的料
I'm nervous. I'm not an actor.
可不 你才不是
Uh, no, you are not.
把它给我
Give me that.
啊哈 啊哈 啊哈
Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh.
行了
Got it.
美味的可可米花是任何早餐的必备品!
Cocoa Puffs are a delicious part of any well-balanced breakfast!
有益健康 父母最爱
They're good for you, which parents love,
糖果味道 我的最爱!
and they taste like candy, which I love!
我忍不住了! 我为可可米花狂!
I can't help it! I'm cuckoo for Cocoa Puffs!
狂!
Cuckoo!
我要流泪了 而且不是因为这房间里长了黑霉
I'm tearing up, and it's not just the black mold in here.
Max 我觉得你把演戏水准定太高了
Max, I think you may have just set the acting bar too high.
哦
Oh.
我从没把酒吧闹得太嗨过(标准定太高)
I've never set a bar too high before.
我只是烧过酒吧 嗨着离开酒吧过
I've set a bar on fire and I've left a bar too high.
嘿 姑娘们
Oh, hey, girls.
介意我在你们这待一会儿吗?
Oh, do you mind if I hang down here with you for a while?
Oleg在楼上 他想色诱我
Oleg is up there, he's trying to seduce me
他正在打扫公寓呢
by cleaning the apartment.
而且那场面 太"肮脏"了
And it's, oh, oh, so dirty.
不好 他在用真空吸尘器 也就是说他也是"真空"的
Oh, oh, he's vacuuming now, which means he's naked.
哎 我和我的波兰价值观啊
Oh, me and my Polish values.
波兰价值观?
Polish Values?
跟我在布鲁克林最喜欢的一元店同名啊
That's the name of my favorite dollar store in Brooklyn.
啊 他在深层清理那团粗毛
Oh, he's deep-cleaning the shag.
天啊 来个人帮帮我
Oh, my God. Somebody, do something
别让我老想着滚床单
to make me not want sex.
好了 Nash 展示下你的台步吧?
All right, Nash, why don't you show us your runway walk?
就这样
That was it.
我还以为你要去拿支笔呢
Oh, I thought you were going to pick up a pen.
谢谢 好极了
Thanks, perfect.
现在性趣全无了
Now I'm completely turned off.
看那家伙走过去 简直出奇地有效
Watching that potato walk across the room really did the trick.
Nash 集中精力
Nash, concentrate.
跟我学
Follow my lead.
右扭 左扭 右扭 左扭
Bam. Pow. Bam. Pow.
前一步右扭 转过身左扭
And step and bam, and step and pow,
退一步右扭!
and step and bam!
这下更好了！
Oh, even better!
看完这个 我可以拿私处
I mean, after that, they could film the sequel
拍"冰雪奇缘"续集了
to Frozen on my lady parts.
同感
Yeah, me too.
因为我的下面"随它吧"
But just 'cause I "Let It Go" down there.
哦 他现在用(飞机杯)吸头了
Oh, now he's using the wand attachment.
哦 他都深入枕间了
Oh, and he's getting real deep between the cushions.
受不鸟了 管他的呢
Oh, my God, just screw it.
老娘憋不到婚礼了!
I'm never gonna make it to the wedding!
Kuchenski祖母 饶过我吧
Oh, Grandma Kuchenski, please forgive me
我就要上了
for what I'm about to do.
我...
I...
你自己也不是什么圣女!
Well, you were no White Lily yourself!
哇哦
Wow.
他走得很熟练
He's bamming and powing up a storm.
他出名了以后希望他还能记得我们
When he's famous, I hope he remembers us.
噗 我觉得我已经做了让他终生难忘的事
Pfft. I'd like to think I did some things he will never forget.
怎么样?
How's that?
非常好 你会走台步
Great, you can walk.
如果你广告词也能念好 我就去喝杯红茶庆祝一下
If you can read too, I'll treat myself to a Snapple.
来读读台词吧
Let's get to the copy.
实际上 我们是有备而来的
Actually, we came prepared.
Nash准备了可可米花的广告
Nash rehearsed the Cocoa Puffs commercial.
我想你会被他打动的
I think you'll be quite moved.
是吗 今天我们要读点
Oh yeah, well, we'll be reading something
不一样的内容
a little different today.
别慌 这种情况经常发生
Don't panic. They do this all the time.
他们就是想看看你能否随机应变
They want to make sure you're flexible.
开始吧 Nash
Yeah. Go ahead, Nash.
不管是什么牌子的麦片 假装它很好吃就行了
Whatever cereal it is, act like it's delicious.
除非是"米脆"的 它们的广告太无聊!
Unless it's Rice Krispies. A-boring!
好的 我开始了
Okay, here goes.
"你知道你喜欢的
"You know you like it.
弯下身去 骚货"
Bend over, bitch."
我们是拿漏了一页吗?
Uh, are we missing a page?
和我小时候知道的麦片广告差太多了
Cereals have changed since I was a kid.
我要读那段发现老师
Should I read the part where I notice
没穿内裤的内容吗?
the teacher's not wearing any panties?
天啊 这是色情片!
Oh, my God. This is porn!
怪不得外面等着的人都好奇怪
No wonder all those people out there were freaks.
怪不得我居然能认出这么多个
No wonder I recognized so many of them.
别大惊小怪的
Don't act so surprised.
是人都知道可可米花就是色情片的代号
Everyone knows Cocoa Puffs is code for porn.
而且你们寄来的照片是个色情作品
Also, you sent us some pictures taken by someone
经验丰富的摄影师拍的
very experienced in erotica.
我们不能让他干这个
We can't let him do this.
我手头有一部明天开拍的电影
I have a movie that starts shooting tomorrow
报酬是一千美元一天
that pays $1,000 a day.
我们能让他干吗?
Can we?
也许不能吧
Maybe we can't.
是在"痛感翘臀"里演主角
It's the lead in Sorest Rump.
也许可以啊
Maybe we can.
Delores 我觉得我们需要私下讨论一下
I think we need a little sidebar, Delores.
我要一起来吗?
Should I come with you?
不 不用
No, we're good.
我有点问题要问试镜演员
I have a couple of questions for the actor.
你会游泳吗 受过割礼吗?
Can you swim, and are you circumcised?
Max 这太过火了
Max, this has gone too far.
我知道 我一开始也只是以为你是来暂住几天
I know, I was expecting you to just crash with me
然后就会找到自己的公寓
for a couple of days and get your own place.
我们真的要为了不让他在餐厅工作
Are we really gonna let Nash do porn
而把他赶去拍色情片吗?
just so he doesn't work at the diner?
小姐们 你们讨论出据结果了吗?
Hey, ladies, what's it gonna be?
我还有很多演员要面试
I got other talent to see.
有个叫Lustin Beaver(恶搞Justin Bieber)的
I got a guy named Lustin Beaver
从费城赶火车过来试镜
taking the Amtrak in from Philly.
Max 如果你真的那么想让我做一个色情演员
Max, if you're really keen on me being a porn actor,
那我就做了
I'll do it.
她说明天他们就要开拍一部叫
She says, tomorrow, they start filming
"大臀盛宴大饭店"的电影
The Grand Booty Fest Hotel.
而且我有口音 他们会多给点钱
And, they'll pay me more for my accent.
还有"为钱掰弯的直男"是什么意思?
Also, what does "gay for pay" mean?
gay for pay: 指为了赚钱而演同性色情片的直男
呃 我觉得那是我们该走了的意思
Ugh, I guess it means we got to go.
Max 你看看他
Look at him, Max.
一个帅小伙 却被演艺圈蚕食并抛弃
A cute guy, eaten up and spat out by show business
和在他之前的所有帅哥一样
like so many Baldwin brothers before him.
Nash根本不在乎做不做模特
Nash doesn't care about modeling.
他才21岁 他什么都不在乎
He's 21. He doesn't care about anything.
他最在乎的就是玩XBox(游戏机)
His biggest concern is playing with the XBox.
我这台 还有最流行的那一款
Mine and, also, the popular video game system.
他在乎你呀
He cares about you.
他甚至愿意为了你去当"为钱掰弯的直男"
He was willing to do "gay for pay".
Nash真的要做"为钱掰弯的直男"吗?
Did I hear Nash is going "gay for pay"?
我口袋里的4美金已经跃跃欲试了
'Cause I've got $4 burning a hole in my pocket.
哦 有顾客来了
Oh, a customer.
欢迎光临"糕潮" 您是来吃甜品的吗?
Hi, welcome to The High. Here for dessert?
谢谢 我从16岁生日之后就不吃甜品了
Oh, thanks but I haven't had cake since my Sweet 16,
而且当时我也把生日蛋糕吐出来了
and even then, I made myself throw it up.
我约了人在这里见面 但我的手机快没电了
I'm meeting someone here and my phone's about to die.
我和手机共存亡 你这里有插座吗?
And if it dies, I will too. Do you have an outlet?
淋雨的时候大叫能帮我缓解焦虑
Screaming in the shower really works for me.
把焦虑宣泄给洗澡水
Like, right into the water.
很有意思 但我真的需要充电器
Super cute. But I do need a phone outlet.
我会给你充电的 亲爱的
I'll plug you in, honey,
当然也会让你的手机电量满格
and I'll take care of your phone, too.
女士们 这是Marie
Girls, meet Marie.
嗨 我说真的 已经只有10%的电了
Hi. Seriously, down to 10%.
噢 你们是在"拉拉约会"网上认识的吗?
Oh, did you two meet on "Lez Meet Up"?
不是 亲爱的 我从来没上过"拉拉约会"网
No, honey, I've never been on "Lez Meet Up".
你说的那个是我 Caroline
Oh, you're thinking of me, Caroline.
我超喜欢女人的尾骨
You know how much I love lady tail.
这地方是在是太棒了
This place is amazing.
很棒不是吗?
Isn't it amazing?
我让室内装潢师重做了九遍
I had the decorator redo it nine times.
你可以感受到他的怒火从墙壁里渗出来
You can feel his anger in the walls.
令人兴奋
It's electric.
我们很来电 这个尤物是谁?
We're electric. Who is this miracle?
他是Nash 我在鲍厄里
That's Nash. I found him in the Bowery
一堆焚烧的垃圾旁边找到他的
next to a pile of burning trash.
去打个招呼
Go say hi.
靠近看你会发觉他更加鲜嫩 秀色可餐
He's even creamier and more delicious up close.
你在吃东西? 太朋克风了
You're eating? That is so punk rock.
快告诉我你的情况
Tell me everything right now.
好吧 我是个洗碗工
Uh, well, I'm a dishwasher.
我来自爱尔兰
I'm from Ireland.
我之前想当个模特
Oh, I was trying to become a model
然后一小时之前我差点就去演色情片了
and I almost did porn an hour ago.
这是我听过最棒的故事了
That is the best story I ever heard.
站起来再讲一遍刚刚的故事
Tell it to me again standing up.
但是这次别用说的
But this time, don't talk.
颜值可以 臀部不错 是个模特的料
I see face, I see ass, I see model.
你有经纪人吗?
Do you have a manager?
我觉得应该是Caroline 那边那个金发的
I guess that'd be Caroline, the blonde one over there.
金发的女孩 过来和我聊聊你的委托人
Blonde one, come over here and talk to me about your client.
我爱上他了 他简直完美
I am in love. He's perfection.
Marie Prower 市场部高级副总监
Marie Prower, Senior VP of Marketing.
太棒了 哪家公司的?
Sweet, what company?
Guess(你猜)
Guess.
汤米·希尔费格(美国休闲领导品牌)
Um, Tommy Hilfinger.
亲爱的 我是Guess公司的
I work for Guess, darling.
什么都别说了 听着
No more words. Listen.
他棒极了
He's amazing.
我想要在tweet上宣传他的 可惜我手机没电了
I would tweet about him right now, but my phone is dead.
所以你们周一把他带到我办公室来一趟
So bring him into my office on Monday.
你听到她说的了 Caroline
You heard her, Caroline.
明天把他带去她办公室
Bring him into her office tomorrow.
她已经迷上我了
She's obsessed with me.
Max 我没看错 他是个模特的料
Max, I was right. He is a model.
给我找个性感的老婆 然后我再和另一个性感的女人出轨
Get me a hot wife and a hotter woman to cheat on her with,
我可是个大牌经纪人
'cause I'm a big-time talent manager.
恭喜啊
Congratulations, dude.
如果这件事成功的话 我可能要辞去
Well, I guess if this works out, I'm gonna have to quit my job
餐厅的工作了
at the diner.
你会生我的气吗?
Will you be mad at me?
我会非常伤心的
I'll be really sad.
我会很想念你的 知道吗?
I'm gonna miss you a lot, you know?
不能时时刻刻见到你
Not seeing you 24/7.
但如果我阻止你追求梦想的话
But I would hate myself if I didn't let you
我会恨死我自己的
follow your dreams.
即使那意味着你要搬出去住了
Even if it means you moving out of the apartment, too.
去吧
Now go.
眼泪都流出来了
Here comes that tear again.
我都要哽咽了
I'm all choked up.
Max 你演罗莎·帕克斯一定很棒
Max, you would have made a great Rosa Parks.
如果你是黑人的话
If you had been black
我猜他们关注的点就是这个
which I guess is what they insist on.
但至少你让他搬出去了! 你真棒
But you got him to move out! You are good.
他也许长得是帅 不过...
Yeah, well, I mean... he is cute, but...
但我也没那么为他痴狂
I'm not all that coo coo for his Cocoa Puffs.